Yes! I'll keep you hooked on Ikiri World whether you're asleep or awake!
I'm Yuki Wrinkiki, a.k.a. Ikiri!
Today I would like to make a makeup video for the first time in a while!
Please excuse me for not wearing any makeup.
I wonder what makeup I should wear today!
Oh, the latest! I'm going to do the latest makeup.
I'm going to do the latest makeup I've been doing lately!
Today's makeup is "My Melo".
Okay! I've finished putting on the lotion, so I'm going to do it!
First of all, I'll start with this.
I forgot my mirror today, so I'm going to use this mirror that I found in Mr. S's car.
I'm going to use this to hide my pores.
And for the primer, I went and bought this right away!
Makalyn told me about this one from Jill Stuart.
Crystal Bloom Lip Bouquet Serum No. 2!
She told me that it makes my lips look like they're coming out of my mouth.
I'm going to apply this.
And this is also what she taught me!
I'm going to apply this on my face!
It's soooooooooooooooooooo good on my face!
It tones up my skin a lot and makes it look like I'm wearing pink fillet. This is amazing! I highly recommend it.
And to make my skin a little more translucent, I applied Givenchy's Prismatic Libre Skincare Ring Corrector.
Why are the names of these products so long?
Here it is!
It's light blue and makes your cheeks look a little more translucent. Concealer first, I've been using this concealer brush lately.
I've been using this Luna concealer from Credo Beau, which Dr. Wonjongyo taught me about. You can use a little bit more of this. I put a little bit of this concealer on my hand, take it from here, and use the brush to conceal dark circles and so on.
I'm going to apply it from the bottom to the top. It's like covering up with the foundation first.
I put this one on top of the other one.
I've been seeing a lot of clouds lately.
And this reddish color.
Well, I'm going to hide it afterwards.
Just in case.
I'm just going to put a little bit of it on.
Now I've covered the foundation with concealer. And the cushion foundation today.
Oh, my God, there's a lot of stuff in the reflection.
Are you okay?Are you okay?
Fitting cushionglow for bonjon.
I'm going to use No. 1 pale pink.
I really should use a sponge like this.
But I only found a sponge that was too dirty.
I'm going to use this one today.
It covers well while leaving a great shine.
It doesn't break down too much, but it doesn't break down too easily either.
The way it blends out is beautiful.
I've been using this for long hours of recording and recently I've been using it all the time.
COSME DECORTE Concealer
Tone Perfecting Palette No. 00.
It's a bright color.
For dark circles and acne.
And acne.
Oh, it disappears suddenly after all.
For acne scars and redness, I'm going to use orange to hide it.
And I want to get rid of the redness around here.
Addiction's Skin Reflective Blush.
Fresh? It says "blush.
Concealer No. 001.
It's a hard, bright concealer like this.
It's a light concealer.
It's a little bit of a blush, but I only do it when I have time, not every day.
I only do this when I have time. Not every day, but every day.
When I have time, I'm a little more careful here.
I'll pull it up a little bit.
If I lighten this area a little bit
I think it makes my nose look a little thinner.
Finished! Finished!
What should I do with the powder today?
I don't know where it comes from.
I don't even know how to read it!
But it's number 2.
Is it some kind of Chinese cosmetic?
It's my favorite, too.This is also my favorite
I love potato starch powder.
If your forehead is sticky, your bangs will be sticky too.
the bangs will be sticky too.
So I used this.
Oh! Almost there!
And with a brush.
Let's do a hand moco.
Let's do this all today.
I don't want you to do anything new here.
And...
And with a fine brush, dust under the eyes with a fine powder so it won't smudge.
I'm going to use this one today, Addiction the eyeshadow palette number 005, this pinkish one.
Like this orange-salmon pink color here.
I want to use it in this case. I don't know the name of the Korean cosmetics.
This is a monochromatic pink, it's a light red light pink, and I'm going to apply this to the torso first. Dr. Wonjoi Won taught me how to do this.
I put this on the eyes and the border between the eyes and the skin.
Then, apply the salmon color of the addiction.
Then, put on this salmon color of Addiction.
This color is cute because it's not too pink.
Cute!
Put this color on and spread it out, and bring it down a little bit like this.
Like this. Darker.
Put this much color like this.
And this brown underneath.
A little bit narrower than where I just put it.
It's like a base color.
Like this. It's a nice touch.
Put it on and draw it on the tip of the eyebrow.
Once you stop the upper eyeshadow with this.
And now, let's go to the eyebrows.
Here are the eyebrows.
Elegance eyebrow slim.
It's this pencil thing.
Use this pencil to make the hairs flow first.
And then use this pencil for the base of the lower part of the eyebrows.This pencil is the foundation for the bottom of the bottom.
It's like straightening out the bottom.
This is the part that's a little bit thin here.
I'm going to add with this.
For the eyebrows, I'm going to use Can Make Mixed Eyebrow Color C01.
I'm going to use this pink color.
When you wear pink makeup, it's recommended to use pink eyebrows as well.
Take the color in the middle.
This gap
Ouch!
Fill in the gaps.
Lately, I've been into eyebrows that look a little more natural and drooping.
I recommend using a slightly thicker brush like this one.
I recommend pulling the brush away from the mirror to get the right balance.
What do you think?
I have an eyebrow mascara that I highly recommend!
It's really bad.
It's called Rom And.
I'm number 3!
I highly recommend this for beginner eyebrows!
If you don't open them in one shot!
I've been saying this a lot lately.
I've been saying this a lot lately, but I recommend eyebrows that are one tone lighter than your hair color!
This is already like a very natural eyebrow bleach.
This one is a little brighter.
I highly recommend this!
Clip the lower lashes.
I'll raise my lashes and draw some eyeliner.
Cammake Creamy Touch Eyeliner No. 2
Lately, I've been filling in the crease of my eyelashes.
I've been trying to fill in the crease of my eyelashes so that when I open my eyes, it doesn't look like I'm drawing eyeliner.
I fill in the crease really well.
And finally, I open up a little space at the bottom of the lash line.
I fill in the perfect line that doesn't make the eyes look droopy or bouncy.
It's not very bouncy or droopy.
Yes!Yes!
I'm OK with this for now.
I think I'll do the bottom one too.
Riidol, Akari's.
Easy Eyeliner 10101
Monedari Pink.
It's this kind of pink color.
It makes it look like a mucous membrane.
I put it under the eyes, a little bit wider on the inner side.
The middle part is like this.
From the edge of the eye lash like this.
This will make the omens look like this.
The main part is relaxed.
I'm going to put pink here like this.
And then we're going to do the u-pink.
These bottom two from this eye palette are on the lower lid.
Take this color on the bottom left, the dewy color, and take this fine brush and apply it like this.
I'm going to layer it here from the outer edge of the dark eye down like this.
Like this.
I think it makes the pencil look more natural.
And next, take this black and brown color here.
Then take this black and brown color and apply it to the triangular part of the eye.
Go down to the outer corner of the eye and vice versa, and go on and on.
This makes the eyes look bigger.
Okay, we're done. And now we're going to do the nose.
Take Lior Skin Forever Couture Luminizer No. 02 Pink Glow and put it on your finger.
I'm not going to put it in here on the nose, I'm going to put it in vertically from here with my finger, straight down.
I bought it as a replacement for the 9 eyes, but I've been using it as a highlighter for the tip of my nose, too.
I'm going to take a little bit with a thin brush and put it on the tip of my nose where I want it to look the most tweeziest.
I'm going to put a little bit of it with a thin brush on the part of the nose where I want it to be the most prominent.
I'm going to put this on the place where I want the tip of the nose to be the sharpest, and I'm going to put it here.
This is something I saw on Twitter.
I saw this on Twitter, and it's a picture of about four cute girls from Nogizaka.
All of them have a sparkle right here.
Right.
That's how you make a fake one.And then we make a fake nose.
And then I shave the nose.
I use a thin brush like this.
I use a grayish color.
But depending on your skin color, you can use a brownish color as well.
I'm going to use this glazed tone from Lilimu.
You can see it right there.
I put some powder in the gray color and apply this gray color.
This will make it less smudgy.
It becomes more even.
Avoid the part where I just made it look like this.
First of all, make a V shape.
It's better to do it inward than outward.
I feel like it's going to be sharpened more and more beautifully.
And also, shave a little bit of this nose vertically.
It looks good now.
And next, under the eyebrows, here. You can say this, don't put it right at the edge here, but put it at an angle. If you make an indentation here, and if you make an indentation here, this part will come out on its own. Can you see the difference? This part will be indented a little bit. I haven't done this one yet, but you should be able to see a little bit of a dent here. I think it is like this. I'll work hard on the opposite.
Lately, I've been playing music at home, music that I'm addicted to,
It's the music from Animal Forest.
The background music changes every two hours.
And then there's the music for the opening screen.
Do you know the music of the opening screen?
I think people who are playing it now would understand it very well.
I like "teettettttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttttt!
I'm the girl who quit junior high summer cram school because I was too addicted to Animal Forest.
When I hear this, I feel really emo. It reminds me of junior high school.
I want to do shading with it today.
I should really do this before I do the powder. Andwi's Contour Pen.
Before you do that smooth powder. Use this on the area you want to shave.
Like this.
I'm sorry. I use a dirty sponge.
Please use a clean sponge.
This is a sponge, and I'm going to blur it outward like this.
OK.
Mascara.
Mascara is first as a primer.Mascara is first used as a primer.
Favorite.
This is Etsuse Eye Edition eyelash primer mascara No. 1. I've been working on moving my lashes outward with this mascara lately, because my lashes are noticeably long here, and if I move them up vertically, they look longer and longer.
So I try to apply it only above the middle of the lashes so that I can make the lashes go horizontally. I'm sorry to use Twitter again, but I think I saw an interview with Satomi Ishihara.
There was a lot of buzz about an interview with Satomi Ishihara, and she said that if you only apply the eyelashes above the middle of the eyelashes, light will enter your eyes and make them look sparkling.
It makes your eyes look sparkling. So I took it to heart.
It's pretty good because it gives a sense of being out of the ordinary. I'll only apply the middle. Let's go for the lower lashes too. This way.
This mascara from Deja Vu. I think I like black mascara these days.
I wonder if it's better to apply the lower half to the lower lashes too?
Let's give it a try.
I'm starting to think so.
If you only apply the lower lashes from the middle down, it will look more natural.
If you apply it below half of your lower lashes as much as possible.
It's good, isn't it?
Very good.
If you draw it on the mucous membrane, it will make your eyes look more defined.
The mucous membrane line is a little too close to the eye.
I use it when I'm in the moment... and I'm also in the moment on YouTube.
I use this when it's the moment of truth.
It makes my eyes pop.
But it's in contact with the mucous membrane...
It's hard to say in a loud voice that I highly recommend it.
I'm going to apply blush.
Here! Try not to go outside right now.
A little bit of a base here.
This close to the eyes.
The position of the blush will probably vary depending on your bone structure.
I think the position of the blush should be different depending on your bone structure.
so you may have to look for it.
And next, this pale pink blush.
I can already see the bottom of this one.
I always forget!
A-pyuh, opyuh...
You always say that, don't you?
Opyu?
And they always say it was an Opium.And then it always says on the ticker that it was an a-pyoo.
Wait a minute, which one is it?
Pink No. 07.
This is a thin brush like this?
Much thinner than a blush brush.
Right here on the eye? I don't think that's where you're supposed to put the blush.
I think.
I put it here because it looks the most natural to me.
I put my blush here.
It doesn't look like I'm wearing blush. I don't feel like I'm wearing blush.
It's more natural and a little bit pinky-pinky from here.
This is where the pink becomes stronger.
And I want to add some more lashes.
I think I'll do this today.
This is another mascara for Bonjon.
Sheer black.
I'm going to add a little bit more of this on top, and I'm going to do it at an angle.
I like this one because it gives a natural bunchy look.
Sweep it side to side like this.
Like this.
Now let's finish the lip.
I'm going to use a pink lip pencil, number 2 here from Heart Percentage.
My upper lip is a little thin on me, so I'm going to fake it to make it look a little bit bigger.
So I'm going to fake it to make it look a little bigger.
And now that my hot brower is warmed up
I'm going to lower my lower lashes as much as possible.
I'm going to do my upper lashes.
When I hot brow the lashes at the end.
You're going to get a bunch.
Oh, not bunches.
I'm going to use the heat to clean up the bunching and everything.
Oh, the lashes look nice and fluffy.
And the lip is Fujiko
Nuance Wrap Tint Beauce limited edition color.
I'm going to apply this first as a base
Pink own baseUnder my pink self.
Cute.
It looks like your original lip color.
Apply this to the base first.
It gives a glossy look.
And then I apply Laka.
Korean Cosmere Lacquer No. 201.
It's a color called Milo.
It's a reddish-pink color.
This kind of color.
It's a little bit like a euphink.
It's got a lot of shine to it.
I'm going to apply this for a while.
Cute adult!
Cute adult color.
I don't think it's a color for everyone.
Super cute! Great!
Like this.
I like it.
The last step.
I'm going to put a little bit of highlighter on.
Lior's Backstage Face Glow Palette #4 in Rose Gold.
I'm going to use this.
I'm going to use a brush about this size, and I'm going to start with the white color on the bottom left here.
And also on your forehead.
Oh, but the most important thing is this.
And also, put it on the tip of your chin, put it in a round shape.
And this
C part.
And you know what?
I forgot something.
I want to tell you something.
With this shading, take this area of brown.
And put it around this circle that I just put here.
Around the circle.
Put it like this.Put it like this.
I think I said the exact same thing, that I thought it would make the chin look like it's coming out here.
I think I said the exact same thing, and then at the end, I want to open up the tear troughs a little bit... but, you know, I want to put some lame on there.
I'm going to put the lame that I just put on, the Addiction lame, and I'm going to take my finger and I'm going to put it on the top of the eye, not on the crease, but on the top of the eye.
And then I'll take a thin brush and put a little bit of the lamé I just put on the inside of here.
Just a little bit of sparkle here and it's really pretty.
Finally, I'm going to put a little bit of that glittery highlight on the tear ducts.
Take this thin brush and put a little bit of this on the tear ducts.
Put a little bit of this here. It's okay if you can't tell if it's on or not.
If you put too much, your eyes will be drawn to the tear ducts.
So if you put a little bit of glitter like this...
Finished! I did it!
It's done! Yay!
Today's makeup was completed again. This is the latest makeup.
The point is to put glitter on the tip of the nose, and to put glitter here where I think Nogizaka-chan is cute, and to put pink blush under the eyes.
I also put pink blush under the eyes. This is my latest makeup style that I've been doing a lot lately!
I'm sure you'll be interested in the latest makeup items I'm buying right now.
I'd love to hear what you think of the newest makeup products you're using, or if there's anything you find useful in my makeup style.
That's all for now! Yukirinu, that's all for now! See you soon!
[ED